Class of 1951 Records, 1947-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1951 Records
1947-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1951.
RG 80 UUID:0a4271e9-18dd-47d1-8b89-de59fb0f4190
7 boxes (2.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1951.
Historical Note
The Class of 1951 was the seventy-third graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1951 Records, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1951, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1951 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Dramatics 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Music 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Photographs 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 4)
- Commencement-Speaker 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1947-1948 (Box 2175, Folder 6)
- Groups 1947-1951 (Box 2175, Folder 7)
- History 1947 (Box 2175, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 11)
- Class Letters 1967-1976, 2002 (Box 2175, Folder 12)
- Officers 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 13)
- Organization (Box 2175, Folder 14)
  See Class of 1949 Organization
- Reunions 1952 (Box 2175, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 2175, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 2175, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 2175, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2175, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1976 (Box 2175, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1976-1981 (Box 2175, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 2175, Folder 22)
- Reunions-Correspondence Newsletters (Box 2175, Folder 23)
- Songs 1996-2001 (Box 2175, Folder 24)
- Sophomore Carnival 1949-1951, n.d. (Box 2175, Folder 25)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1949 (Box 2175, Folder 26)
- Step Sings 1949 (Box 2175, Folder 27)
- Who's Who 1947 (Box 2175, Folder 28)
- 50th Reunion Book 2001 (Box 2175.1, Folder 1)
- Reunion Book Addendum/Errata 2001 (Box 2175.1, Folder 2)